https://www.pencomdesign.com/privacy-policy/

All board products Proudly made in USA!
My Account
Orders
Comparison list
Wish list
Track my order(s)
Track my order(s)
Sign inRegister
Email
PasswordForgot your password?
Checkout
Manufacturer of computer controlled relay, I/O and custom boards for commercial and industrial applications.
Please Note:
We are now open for normal business operation - however due to the virus we have minimal staff so delays in production will be inevitable.  We will do our best to complete all orders asap.
Menu
Newest Products
Home/Privacy policy
Relay BoardsGeneral PurposeRS232 Control1 ChannelAC Wall Adapter
DC Terminal Block Power
120V 50/60Hz Power
240V 50/60Hz Power
2 ChannelAC Wall Adapter
DC Terminal Block Power
120V 50/60Hz Power
240V 50/60Hz Power
8 ChannelAC Wall Adapter
USB Bus powered
Relay Boards With I/OGeneral PurposeRS232 Control1 ChannelAC Wall Adapter
DC Terminal Block Power
120V 50/60Hz Power
240V 50/60Hz Power
2 ChannelAC Wall Adapter
DC Terminal Block Power
120VAC 50/60Hz power
240VAC 50/60Hz power
8 ChannelAC Wall Adapter
Privacy policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.pencomdesign.com
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or mailing address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, please email this request to our sales department addrees located in the Contact Us section of our website.
How do we protect your information?
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information).
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone!
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  However we treat offline data with the same security as we would for the online data.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
© 2000-2020 Pencom Design, Inc.  PO Box 645, Trumbauersville, PA 18970-0645,
All Rights Reserved
